<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="resume.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<cv>
    <me name="Ijeoma Chickwekwem" address="3837 Bloomington Crescent, Mississauga ON" telephone="(647)542-2613" email="ijeomachikwekwem@gmail.com" />
    <education>
        <qualification establishment="Calisota University" type="Degree" from="2006" to="2009">
            Bachelor of Science – Computing Science
            <strong>(CGPA 3.55/4.0)</strong>
        </qualification>
    </education>
    <employment>
        <experience establishment="Transcom Worldwide" job_title="Technical Support Advisor" from="AUG 2020" to="Present">
            <description>(Tools: Core, iCloud, Gather, Safeview, Microsoft Outlook)</description>
            <achievement>Provided exceptional technical phone support for Apple Products (iPhone, iPad, Apple Watch, Apple Accessories, etc.)</achievement>
            <achievement>Investigated and resolved customer inquiries and complaints in a timely and empathetic manner</achievement>
            <achievement>Handled a large amount of calls every day but made sure each customer’s concern is addressed and resolved.</achievement>
            <achievement>Consulted user guides, technical manuals and other relevant documents to research to implement solutions</achievement>
            <achievement>Provide advice training to users on response to identified difficulties</achievement>
            <achievement>Provide business systems, network, and internet support to users in response to identified difficulties</achievement>
            <achievement>Managed wide variety of customer service and administrative tasks to resolve customer issues quickly</achievement>
        </experience>
        <experience establishment="SP Data" job_title="Customer Service and Telesales Representative" from="Apr 2019" to="Jun 2019">
            <description>Retained customers by utilizing key relationship building skills and effective customer service techniques</description>
            <achievement>Successfully presented products by utilizing effective sales and persuasion skills in addition to a solid knowledge of the company’s products and
                competitor’s products</achievement>
            <achievement>Efficiently handled a large volume of calls</achievement>
            <achievement>Strategically provided appropriate resolutions that were optimal solutions for a valued customer base</achievement>
            <achievement>Handled intricate Sprint customer complaints related to their products and services</achievement>
            <achievement>Always maintained professional integrity and customer focus while meeting and exceeding monthly quotas</achievement>
            <achievement>Working with customers to resolve any issues which may be preventing them from maintaining a relationship with Sprint</achievement>
        </experience>
    </employment>
    <projects>
        <project name='Client-Server Program'>
            <point>Tools: Atom Editor, Terminal</point>
            <point>Made a simple client program using C programming. The client program initiates the communication by sending request. The
                server program which runs continuously, waits to receive communication from the client</point>
            <point>• Implemented a time server using socket programming and communicated using User Datagram Protocol (UDP).</point>
        </project>
        <project name='TCP/IP Socket Program'>
            <point>Used Socket programming to write an echo server that utilizes the TCP/IP protocol</point>
        </project>
        <project name='Implemented a Reliable Block Transfer Application'>
            <point>Implemented a reliable block transfer application using the Stop-and-Wait (SWAP) protocol. Both the sender and receiver use a sliding window
                with size 1. The sender sends one packet a time and waits for an acknowledgment before sending the next packet. Added a checksum packet to
                detect corrupted packets.</point>
        </project>
        <project name='Palo Alto Network Topology'>
            <point>Configured appropriate Network Zones (Inside, Outside, DMZ) </point>
            <point>Assigned appropriate interfaces to Network zones</point>
            <point>Configured Branch and LAN Network Topology using Palo Alto Firewall ensuring all hosts can communicate both interzone and intrazone</point>
            <point>Created security and NAT policies to regulate data flow from one zone to another.</point>
            <point>Configured HA for the Corporate Network Firewall</point>
            <point>Established a VPN between Corporate and Branch Networks </point>
        </project>
        <project name='National Bank of Erehwon Database'>
            <point>Tools: Microsoft Excel, Oracle SQL developer</point>
            <point>Description: Developed a database in Oracle that implements a fictional Erehwon Bank scenario. The National Bank of Erehwon handles money
                and maintains bank accounts on behalf of clients. In the database when an account is first opened, its balance is set to zero. During the course of
                day-to-day business, the bank applies transactions to accounts, including deposits, withdrawals, bill payments, and debit purchases or returns.
                For each transaction, the data and time, amount, and accounts are recorded along the reference data applicable to that type of transaction.</point>
        </project>
    </projects>
    <certifications>
        <certificate>OWASP Top 10 (LinkedIn)</certificate>
        <certificate>Vulnerability Management (LinkedIn)</certificate>
        <certificate>CompTIA A+ (CompTIA)</certificate>
        <certificate>CompTIA Network+ (In View)</certificate>
        <certificate>Splunk 7.x Fundamentals (Splunk)</certificate>
        <certificate>Palo Alto Networks Cybersecurity Professional Certificate (Coursera)</certificate>
    </certifications>
</cv>